[
  {
    "question": "IAM's permission delegation mechanism",
    "answer": "Roles"
  },
  {
    "question": "Route 53",
    "answer": "Scalable Domain Name System"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cloudfront",
    "answer": "Content Delivery Network service"
  },
  {
    "question": "SNS",
    "answer": "AWS Managed \"push\" Notification service"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fargate",
    "answer": "Run containers without mnanaging underlying infrastructure."
  },
  {
    "question": "CloudTrail",
    "answer": "Monitors account API activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Advantages of using RDS as a DBA",
    "answer": "Simplified administration tasks"
  },
  {
    "question": "Architecture used for High Availability with EC2",
    "answer": "Auto Scaling Group with an Elastic Load Balancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "S3 bucket poliy element used to grant users access",
    "answer": "Principal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cost-effective EC2 Instance type for interruptible workloads",
    "answer": "Spot Instances"
  },
  {
    "question": "An EC2 hosted PostgreSQL DB needs to be updated for HA and DR",
    "answer": "Migrate to RDS, enable the Multi-AZ feature"
  }
]
